Look, we have only covered some of the basics here today.
I want to point out where you can find some more information to continue your agent journey.
We've covered a lot of info.
Here are some of my favorite resources for diving deeper into all that we just talked about.
The Langtrain documentation is a great place to start.
Specifically, it provides a great high-level overview of all the packages and services
in the Langtrain ecosystem.
So we break down the different Langtrain core packages as well as all the Langtrain community
packages.
So we use Tavilia as part of Langtrain community and then we also use Langtrain OpenAI, which
is a separate partner package.
But we have a ton of other integrations and you can explore those here.
Langtrain itself is more high-level and covers agents and other chains and different retrieval
strategies that are good high-level entry points if you just want to get started.
We also have a bunch of templates that can be deployed easily with Langserve.
Langserve is just a really easy way to turn your Langtrain application into a web server.
Helping out with all of this is Langsmith.
From the beginning, Langsmith can help with debugging and then it can also help with monitoring
and production and it also has a playground, which we saw earlier.
Looking at a few other sites, the Langtrain GitHub repo has a lot of good resources, a lot
of good cookbooks and a lot of templates for getting started.
The Langgraph repo, of course, has in-depth documentation on Langgraph, everything that
we just covered, so great reference docs, great tutorials and great Pouch2 guides.
We've also done previous courses on Langtrain with deep learning that I'd highly recommend
checking out in particular functions, tools, and agents with Langtrain is a really good precursor
to this lesson.
We already saw the prompt hub once, but just to reiterate, this is a great place to go
to get inspiration and see what other expert prompters are doing.